Inventory of the Thomas H. (Thomas Hawkins) Johnson Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- White House Science Council (WHSC) (Box 30)
  - Background materials and forms, 1976-1982 (Folder 30: 1)
    Includes letter, memoranda, organizational chart, and procedural manual
  - Letter, list of members, memoranda, notes, travel authorization forms and worksheet, 1981-1983 (Folder 30: 2)
  - Meetings
    Includes minutes and related materials
    - 1982
      - March 9 (Folder 30: 3)
      - May 20 (Folder 30: 4)
      - July 16 (Folder 30: 5)
      - September 17 (Folder 30: 6)
      - November 19 (Folder 30: 7)
    - 1983
      - January 21 (Folder 30: 8)
      - March 18 (Folder 30: 9)
  - Press, 1982 (Folder 30: 10)
    Article and clippings
- Superconducting Super Collider (SSC), 1988-1989 (Folder 30: 11)
  Article, clipping, comments on budgetary risks, letter, outline, report, and study
- White House Science Council (WHSC) (Box 31)
  - Federal lab panel, 1982 (Folder 31: 1-2)
    Article, clipping, graphs, instructions for review, letters, list of interagency laboratory working group, memoranda, minutes of meetings, report, and study relating to the review of federal laboratories in the context of reported under-performance
  - Special Nuclear Materials Production panel, 1982 (Folder 31: 3)
    Letters, memoranda, minutes of meetings, notes, and schedule relating to the issue of nuclear materials production and maintenance of the stockpile
  - Letters, list of WHSC federal laboratory review panel members, memoranda, note, report, and schedule of study and inspection of laboratories, 1982-1983
  - Office of Science and Technology Development (OSTD), 1981 (Box-folder 32: 1)
    Article, clipping relating to the appointment of George Keyworth as President Ronald Reagan's science advisor. Includes reassignment order for Thomas Johnson as a consultant to the presidential science advisor in Washington, D.C. for one year
  - Military technology panel, 1982 (Folder 32: 2)
    Agenda, energy study, letters, list of associate members of the WHSC, memoranda, notice and schedule of meeting, and travel schedule, relating to the role of the panel in connection with the inspection of advanced weapon technology
  - Memoranda to the WHSC regarding scheduled meetings, 1982 (Folder 32: 3)
    Includes a letter to Edward Teller
  - Members' extraneous correspondence, 1982 (Folder 32: 4)
    Includes a memorandum to Edward Teller
  - Procedural manual, 1982 (Folder 32: 5)
  - Active--List of members of the WHSC, 1982-1983 (Folder 32: 6)
    Includes notice of establishment of the WHSC and notes
  - Other panels--List of members of the Defense Science Board (DSB), 1982 (Folder 32: 7)
- Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), 1974-1982 (Folder 32: 8)
  Includes articles, bulletins, letter, list of members of the panel on the national airspace system plan proposed by the FAA, memoranda, notes, notice of meeting, and report on the plan
- Miscellaneous materials relating to the national airspace system, agenda for panel discussion, financial record relating to the implementation of the plan, mission statement and report from the Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), air traffic control system, and reports on the plan and preparation and consequences of an earthquake as prepared by the Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1978-1982
- "Gas Laser Technology," Douglas C. Sinclair and W. Earl Bell, undated (Box-folder 33: 1)
- Mission Research Corporation (MRC) reports for the Defense Nuclear Agency (DNA)
  - "Encyclopedia of High-Altitude Nuclear Weapons Effects," Vol. II, 1972-1975
  - "Physics of High-Altitude Burst Effects,", 1977
- White House Science Council manual, 1982
- Note, undated
- Pamphlets--United States Military Academy, West Point, New York, 1982 (Box-folder 34: 1)
  Includes brochure, letter, memoranda, schedule of religious services, and newsletter
- Bulletin of the American Physical Society, 1988
- Course outline and notes, prepared by Thomas Johnson for a class on plasma dynamics, Institute of Technology, U.S. Air Force, 1979
- "Encyclopedia of High-Altitude Nuclear Weapons Effects," Vol. II, 1973-1975
  Report prepared by the Mission Research Corporation (MRC)
- "Statistical Mechanics and Kinetic Theory of Plasmas," Carl Tyler Case, 1970
- "Numerical Studies of Resistive Instabilities in Diffuse Pinches,", 1974
- Notes for an advanced weapons technology course, Institute of Technology, U.S. Air Force, 1979
- "Readings in National Security," Vol. II, national security seminar, Department of Social Sciences, United States Military Academy, West Point, New York, 1982-1983 (Box 35)
- "Physics of Short Wavelength Laser Design," P. L. Hagelstein, 1981
- Summer 1988 Free Electron Laser (FEL) report--Discussions of some major issues
- "Time-Dependent Thermal-Blooming/Turbulence Propagation Code: Design, Motivations, Requirements,", 1987 September 22
  Project report
- Advanced compact reactor systems--Proceedings of a symposium, National Academy of Sciences, Washington, D.C., 1982 November 15-17
- Cadet notebook, national security seminar, Department of Social Sciences, United States Military Academy, West Point, New York, 1982-1983
- "Plasma Physics Aspects of the Solar Neutrino Problem," Robert O. Hunter, Jr., 1981
- Certificate awarded to Thomas H. Johnson by the Honor Society of Phi Kappa Phi in recognition of high scholastic achievement in the 1985-1986 year, United States Military Academy
- "Fusion Reactor Systems," F. L. Ribe, 1975 (Box-folder 36: 1)
  Review
- "Theory of Plasma Transport in Toroidal Confinement Systems," F. L. Hinton and R. D. Hazeltine, 1976 (Folder 36: 2)
- "Motion of Magnetic Lines of Force," William A. Newcomb, 1958 (Folder 36: 3)
- "Linear Oscillations of a Collisionless Plasma," A. Simon, plasma physics seminar, International Atomic Energy Agency, Vienna, 1965 (Folder 36: 4)
  Paper
- Review of Tokamak research by H. P. Furth, 1975 (Folder 36: 5)
- Controlled Thermonuclear Research annual report, Lawrence Livermore Laboratory, University of California, 1973 July – 1974 June (Folder 36: 6)
- "Diffusion, De-Excitation, and Ionization Cross Sections for Metastable Atoms I," Manfred A. Biondi, 1952 (Folder 36: 7)
  Article. Includes related materials
- "Energy Transfer Collisions of Atoms and Molecules," Jean W. Gallagher, 1979 November 1 (Folder 36: 8)
  Bibliography
- "Electron Impact Excitation of the Rare Gases," P. S. Ganas and A. E. S. Green, 1971 (Folder 36: 9)
- "The Role of Electrons in Excimer Lasers," David L. Huestis, 1985 (Folder 36: 10)
  Outline
- Old Krkin draft materials, undated (Folder 36: 11)
- "Dissociate Attachment from Vibrationally and Rotationally Excited HCl and HF," M. Allan and S. F. Wong, 1980 (Folder 36: 12)
- Articles and letter to the editor relating to vibrational excitation of molecules by electron impact; transmission spectroscopy in hydrogen halides; energy deposition mechanism for electrons colliding with F2 and F2 mixtures; and kinetics of formation of chloride ions in atmosphere, 1972-1976 (Folder 36: 13)
- Defense procurement, management, organizational reform, 1980-1985, undated (Folder 36: 14)
  Articles, clippings, notes, and report
- David Allan Rosenberg, 1982-1987 (Folder 36: 15)
- Miscellany, 1984-1987
  Articles, clippings, map, and notes relating primarily to the Strategic Defense Initiative or "Star Wars"
- AIS rough draft, 1980 (Box-folder 37: 1)
  Letter
- Jaws, 1979-1980 (Folder 37: 2)
  Includes correspondence between Thomas Johnson and Pete Rose, E. T. Manning, and Eugene Fubini relating to fusion research and laser applications; memorandum to Dr. Freeman regarding Jaws IV; newsletter; and notes
- News reports/budgets, 1981-1984 (Folder 37: 3)
- Speech, Robert L. Hirsch, Sixth topical meeting on the technology of fusion energy, 1985 March 5 (Folder 37: 4)
- Fusion Power Associates, 1982-1985 (Folder 37: 5)
  Newsletters
- Soloman J. Buchsbaum panel, 1978-1980 (Folder 37: 6)
  Agenda for meeting, articles, budget, comments, letters, list of attendants for sessions of ad hoc experts group on fusion, memoranda, notes, outline, and report relating to fusion research program
- Office of Fusion Energy (OFE) report to Fusion Review Committee, Washington, D.C., 1980 February 13 (Folder 37: 7)
- Princeton Large Torus (PLT) program, 1978 (Folder 37: 8)
  Article, letters to the editor, memoranda, and notes
- Tokamak Fusion Test Reactor (TFTR), 1979-1982 (Folder 37: 9)
  Clippings, program, report, and related materials
- Miscellany, 1977-1981
  Articles, information packet for Princeton Plasma Physics Laboratory, journals, letter, report, and statement by the president relating to the Magnetic Fusion Energy Engineering Act, Tandem mirror plan, and mirror fusion program
- Mirror machines program--Overview, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 38: 1)
  Articles and journal
- "A Reassessment of the Livermore Mirror Program," Ronald C. Davidson, 1978 (Folder 38: 2)
- Mirror Fusion Test Facility (MFTF), 1978-1981 (Folder 38: 3)
  Article, brochures, fact sheet, report, and materials relating to the Tandem mirror fusion program
- Report on the concept review committee recommendations for proof-of-principle alternate concept programs, 1979 March; and articles, "A Triggered-Reconnection Compact Toroid Experiment," A. L. Hoffman and G. C. Vlases, undated; and "Plasma Rotation in Field-Reversed Theta Pinches," L. C. Steinhauer (Folder 38: 4)
- Mirror reactors, 1977-1979 (Folder 38: 5)
  Articles and journals
- Reactors, hybrids, etc., 1971-1982 (Folder 38: 6)
  Articles, journals, remark, and report
- Fusion Materials Irradiation Test (FMIT) project, 1978, undated (Folder 38: 7)
  Articles and draft papers
- Miscellany, 1978-1985
  Address, brochure, journals, and report relating to magnetic fusion and the Tandem mirror fusion program
- Fusion budget strategies, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 39: 1-3)
  Article, budget strategy, letter, memoranda, notes, review of the fusion energy programs, and related materials
- Orange book--Fusion research and development program, undated (Folder 39: 4)
- "The Motion of a Charged Particle in a Strong Magnetic Field," Ira B. Bernstein, undated (Folder 39: 5)
- "Radiation from Plasmas," John M. Dawson, undated, and "Cyclotron Radiation," W. E. Drummond, circa 1965 (Folder 39: 6)
- Princeton experiments, 1976-1977 (Folder 39: 7)
  Articles relating to Tokamak research
- "Plasma and the Controlled Thermonuclear Reaction," P. L. Kapitza, 1979 (Folder 39: 8)
- "Stabilization by Shear and Negative V,", undated (Folder 39: 9)
- Review of fusion projects, 1978 (Folder 39: 10)
  Memoranda concerning budget
- International co-operation, 1978 (Folder 39: 11)
  Article, letter, and remarks
- "Collisional Interchange Instabilities in Shear and Stabilized Systems," B. Coppi and M. N. Rosenbluth, plasma physics seminar, 1965 (Box-folder 40: 1)
- "Toroidal Containment of a Plasma," Harold Grad, 1967 (Folder 40: 2)
- "Stability of the Adiabatic Motion of Charged Particles in the Earth's Field," Theodore G. Northrop and Edward Teller, Argus symposium, National Academy of Sciences, Washington, D.C., 1960 (Folder 40: 3)
- "Electrostatic Instabilities in Finite Mirror Plasmas," R. F. Post and Marshall N. Rosenbluth, circa 1966 (Folder 40: 4)
- Quasi-Linear theory, 1964-1966 (Folder 40: 5)
- "Waves and Turbulence in a Tokamak Fusion Plasma," C. M. Surko and R. E. Slusher, 1983 (Folder 40: 6)
- "Motion of Charged Particles in Electromagnetic Fields," A. I. Morozov and L. S. Solov'ev, undated (Folder 40: 7)
- "Finite-Resistivity Instabilities of a Sheet Pinch," Harold P. Furth, John Killeen, and Marshall N. Rosenbluth, 1963 (Folder 40: 8)
- Soloman J. Buchsbaum panel documentation, 1980-1982 (Folder 40: 9)
  Letters, memoranda, and report
- Magnetic Fusion Advisory Committee (MFAC), 1982 (Folder 40: 10)
  Newsletter, report, and related materials
- "Tokamak Devices," L. A. Artsimovich, 1972 (Folder 40: 11)
- "Trapped Particles in Toroidal Magnetic Systems," B. B. Kadomtsev and O. P. Pogutse, 1971 (Folder 40: 12)
- Hannes Alfvén, 1971 (Folder 40: 13)
  Articles on plasma physics
- "Present Status of Controlled Thermonuclear Theory," Marshall N. Rosenbluth, undated (Folder 40: 14)
- "Controlled Fusion Research and High-Temperature Plasmas," H. F. Post, 1970 (Folder 40: 15)
- "Microinstabilities," Marshall N. Rosenbluth, circa 1965 (Folder 40: 16)
- Plasma fusion research, cyclotron instability, and electrostatic electron-ion streaming instability, 1970-1982
  Articles, memoranda, minutes, and reports
- Fusion policy and fusion energy program, 1978 (Box-folder 41: 1)
  Articles, notes, remarks, report, and statement
- Presentations on Tokamak overview, Tokamak Fusion Test Reactor (TFTR) remote maintenance program, superconducting magnet development, materials technology for ETF, neutral beam heating, Tokamak as commercial power reactors, radio frequency heating, Tokamak stability, beta limits, electron and ion confinement, divertor Tokamak operation, and related programs before the Fusion Review Committee, Energy Research Advisory Board, 1980 (Folder 41: 2-3)
- "Electron Impact Excitation of Atoms," B. L. Moiseiwitsch and S. J. Smith, 1968 (Folder 41: 4)
- Xe total excitation, Makoto Hayashi, 1983 (Folder 41: 5)
- "Near Infrared Gas Lasers," S. Lawton and T. A. DeTemple, 1978 (Folder 41: 6)
- Michal Gryzinski, 1976 (Folder 41: 7)
- "Electron Energy Distribution in E-Beam Generated Xe and Ar Plasmas," C. J. Elliott and A. E. Greene, 1976-1978 (Folder 41: 8)
- "Temperature Dependence of Dissociative Recombination and Molecular-Ion Formation in He, Ne, and Ar Plasmas," Che Jen Chen, 1968-1977 (Folder 41: 9)
- Boltzman code (Box 42)
  - "Total Inelastic Cross Sections for Slow Electrons in Xenon," A. J. Dixon and A. von Engel, 1968, and "Measurement of Townsend Ionization Coefficients and the Breakdown Potentials for the Penning Mixtures of Ne and Kr," Ashok K. Bhattacharya, 1979 (Folder 42: 1)
  - Vriens model for ionization, 1972-1977 (Folder 42: 2)
    Computer printouts, letter, and notes
  - "Calculation of Inelastic Electro-Molecule Collision Cross Sections by Classical Method," Ernest Bauer and Charlotte Decker Bartry, 1965, and "Elastic Scattering of Low-Energy Electrons by Ne, Ar, Kr, and Xe," R. Haberland, L. Fritsche, and J. Noffke, 1986 (Folder 42: 3)
  - "Electron Impact Cross Sections for Argon," L. R. Peterson and J. E. Allen, Jr., 1971 (Folder 42: 4)
  - "Determination of Cross Sections and Oscillator Strengths for Argon by Electron-Energy-Loss Spectroscopy," G. P. Li, T. Takayanagi, K. Wakiya, H. Suzuki, and others, 1988 (Folder 42: 5)
  - "Ionization Cross Sections and Secondary Electron Distributions," A. E. S. Green and T. Sawada, 1972 (Folder 42: 6)
  - "Total Electron Impact Excitation Cross Sections of Ar and Kr," J. H. Jacob and J. A. Mangano, 1976; "Comprehensive Optical and Collision Data for Radiation Action ll. Ar," E. Eggarter, 1975; and "Absolute Determination of the Total Excitation Cross Sections of the Noble Gases by Electron Impact," M. Schaper and H. Scheibner, circa 1975 (Folder 42: 7)
  - H. A. Hyman, 1978-1979 (Folder 42: 8)
  - "Total Cross Sections for the Production of Metastable Neon Atoms by Electron Impact," P. J. O. Teubner, et al., 1985 (Folder 42: 9)
  - "Total Cross Sections for Ionization and Attachment in Gases by Electro Impact. I. Positive Ionization," Donald Rapp and Paula Englander-Golden, 1965 (Folder 42: 10)
    Includes related article, 1973
- Spectra
  - Reactions and spectra, 1979, 1987 (Folder 42: 11)
  - "Krypton-Flouride Excimer Laser Kinetics," Thomas H. Johnson, undated (Folder 42: 12)
    Includes notes
  - "On the Diffusion Approximation of the Boltzmann Equation for Slow Electrons," J. H. Jacob, B. N. Srivastava, M. Rokni, and J. A. Mangano, 1979 (Folder 42: 13)
  - Boltzmann solutions, 1975 (Folder 42: 14-15)
  - Al's problem--Notes, undated (Folder 42: 16)
  - Los Alamos Scientific Laboratory computer, 1985. (Folder 42: 17)
    Memoranda and notes
- Absorbers
  - Dimer ions, 1977-1979 (Folder 42: 18)
    Articles and graphs
  - Xenon manifold, undated. (Folder 42: 19)
  - Configurations/Abstracts, undated (Folder 42: 20)
    Graphs, notes, and tables
  - "Kinetics Considerations for Narrowband XeC1 Lasers," Allen M. Hunter and Robert O. Hunter, Jr., undated (Folder 42: 21)
  - XeC1 spectra, 1975-1978, 1983-1987 (Folder 42: 22)
- Miscellaneous articles--Continuum spectra of gas molecules, radiation and potential of T1-noble gas molecules, extreme-wing line broadening and Cs-Inert-Gas Potential, spectroscopic studies of diatomic noble gas halides, and covalent and ionic states of the xenon halides, 1972-1978
- Ion-molecule reactions of Ar2+, 1979 (Box-folder 43: 1)
- Absorption processes in XeC1, 1979 (Folder 43: 2)
- "Electron Photodeachment Cross Sections of C1- and Br-+," A. Mandl, 1976; "Diatomics-In-Molecules Potential Surfaces for the Triatomic Rare Gas Halides: Rg2X+," D. L. Huestis and N. E. Schlotter, 1977?; "Visible Absorption by Electron-Beam Pumped Rare Gases," Ehud Zamir, David L. Huestis, Howard H. Nakano, and others, 1979; and "UV Transient Absorptions in High Pressure Argon Excited by Relativistic Electrons," F. Collier, J. B. Leblond, F. Hoffbeck, and P. Cottin, 1981 (Folder 43: 3)
- "Photoassociative Laser-Induced Fluorescence of XeC1 and Kinetics of XeC1(B) and XeC1(C) in Xe," J. K. Ku and D. W. Setser, 1984 (Folder 43: 4)
- "Vibrational Excitation of HCl In Electron Beam," R. E. Center, J. H. Jacob, and Z. Rozenberg, 1982 (Folder 43: 5)
- Electron impact dissociation of HC1, 1986 (Folder 43: 6)
- Related lasers: Xe, C1, XeF(C-A), Xe*, 1980-1983 (Folder 43: 7)
- Electron quenching, 1979-1980 (Folder 43: 8)
- Quenching of Xenon, 1985-1986 (Folder 43: 9)
  Article and letter
- Charge transfer and penning ionization, 1980-1981 (Folder 43: 10)
- David L. Huestis, 1977-1985 (Folder 43: 11)
- Don Setser, 1973-1980 (Folder 43: 12)
- Destruction of XeC1(X), R. W. Waynant and J. G. Eden, 1980 (Folder 43: 13)
- Arthur Greene, 1981 (Folder 43: 14)
  Memorandum
- Laser systems, 1979-1981 (Folder 43: 15)
- AVCO, undated (Folder 43: 16)
  Graphs and reports
- "Ion-Atom Reactions in Rare Gases," A. V. Phelps, 1977 (Folder 43: 17)
- Don Lorents, 1979-1987 (Folder 43: 18)
- Palumbo code, 1982-1983 (Folder 43: 19)
  Computer printouts
- SRI International workshop on XeC1 laser development and performance, Menlo Park, California, 1985 December 18 (Folder 43: 20)
- AVCO Everett Research Laboratory, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 44: 1)
  Letters, report, and study
- Naval Research Laboratory (NRL), 1978-1982 (Folder 44: 2)
  Articles and report
- Mathematical Sciences Northwest, Inc. (MSNW), 1981-1982 (Folder 44: 3)
- SRI International, 1973, 1982
- Laser systems, 1976-1987
  Article and reports
- Mathematical Sciences Northwest, Inc. (MSNW) electron density measurements, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 45: 1)
  Articles. Includes graphs, letters, notes, and reports
- "Electron-Beam XeC1 Laser with a Specific Output Energy of 20 J/Liter," A. D. Klementov, N. V. Morozov, and P. B. Sergeev, 1985 (Folder 45: 2)
- "Preionization Kinetics of an X-Ray Preionized XeC1 Gas Discharge Laser," H. Shields, A. J. Alcock, and R. S. Taylor, 1983 (Folder 45: 3)
- Laser systems, 1980-1986 (Folder 45: 4)
  Articles and related materials
- "Efficient E-Beam Excitation of XeC1 (B)," Dietmar E. Rothe and Mani L. Bhaumik, 1979 (Folder 45: 5)
  Article. Includes graphs, notes, and related materials
- Western Research Corporation (WRC), undated (Folder 45: 6)
  Data and graphs
- AVCO Everett, 1979-1980, undated
- Proceedings of the EMRLD technical interchange meeting sponsored by the Strategic Defense Initiative Office, 1984
- XeCl JAP paper: Useful back-up, 1981 (Box-folder 46: 1)
  Articles, charts, graphs, notes, and report
- XeCl raw materials, undated (Folder 46: 2)
  Graphs, list of references, and notes
- Workshop on XeCl Kinetics, SRI International, Menlo Park, California, 1986 March 10 (Folder 46: 3)
- "XeCl Laser Modeling," Thomas C. Genoni and Thomas H. Johnson, 1984 (Folder 46: 4)
- "Physics of the Krypton Fluoride Laser," Thomas Johnson and Allen M. Hunter, 1980 (Folder 46: 5)
- Temperature model, undated (Folder 46: 6)
- Absorption, emission calculation for Xe Cl, 1976-1986 (Folder 46: 7)
  Article, letter, and report
- "Electron Densities in Xenon Chloride Laser Mixtures," Thomas Johnson and H. E. Cartland, 1988 (Folder 46: 8)
  Includes article, copyright agreement, and letter
- KSOF model, Kannari and others, 1983 (Folder 46: 9)
- XeF model, 1978-1987 (Folder 46: 10)
- Bill Long, undated (Folder 46: 11)
- Mathematical Sciences Northwest, Inc. (MSNW) model, 1981 (Folder 46: 12)
- Sandia simulations, undated (Folder 46: 13)
  Graphs
- AVCO experiment simulations, undated (Folder 46: 14)
- Western Research Corporation (WRC) simulation, undated (Folder 46: 15)
- Jacob simulations, undated (Folder 46: 16)
- Aspen Strategy Group summer workshop, Aspen, Colorado
  - "The Strategic Defense Initiative and American Security,", 1986 August 10-15 (Folder 46: 17)
    Agenda, letter, list of members and office holders, map, memoranda, newsletter, notes, outline of paper by Thomas Johnson, and schedule
  - "Rethinking the Role of Nuclear Weapons in U.S. National Strategy,", 1987 August 16-21 (Folder 46: 18)
    Address list, article, letters, map, memoranda, notes, and programs
- USSR II--Joint meeting of Federation of American Scientists (FAS) and Committee of Soviet Scientists for Peace and against the Nuclear Threat, Virginia, 1987 April 24-26 (Folder 46: 19)
  Includes agenda, agreement, letters, and related materials
- Tenure committee--Appointment of Professor and Head, Department of System Engineering, United States Military Academy (USMA), 1987-1988 (Folder 46: 20)
  Letters, list of applicants, and memoranda
- Note, undated
- UAV memoranda, 1987 (Box-folder 47: 1)
  Article, map, note, and report
- Jack Matlock memoranda on Strategic Defense Initiative (SDI), 1984-1987 (Folder 47: 2)
  Letter, memoranda, and note
- National Training Center (NTC), 1986-1987 (Folder 47: 3)
  Article, letter, memoranda, newsletter, and program
- Scientific aspect of global security, 1987-1988 (Folder 47: 4)
  Includes agenda and minutes of meeting, article, letter, and memoranda
- SDI red team review group, 1988 (Folder 47: 5)
  Agenda, list of reference, and memoranda
- SRL--Research proposal for the United States Military Academy (USMA), 1986 (Folder 47: 6)
  Memoranda, notes, and report
- House Armed Services Committee (HASC), 1988 (Folder 47: 7)
  Article, form letter in support of Strategic Defense Initiative (SDI), message, and testimony
- American Academy ABM study, 1988 (Folder 47: 8)
  Chapter titles for "Managing the ABM Treaty Regime," letter from Richard L. Garwin to Thomas Johnson, list of working group members' addresses and phone numbers, memoranda, testimony, and related materials
- Department of Energy (DOE) and United States Military Academy (USMA) inter-agency agreement, 1980-1988 (Folder 47: 9)
  Includes article, agreement form, letter, memoranda, note, and statement of work
- Stanford regional security study, 1988 (Folder 47: 10)
  Memoranda and report
- Department of Energy/IDP, 1989 (Folder 47: 11)
  Chart, list of individuals in the assistant secretary of defense programs, and miscellany
- New Republic, 1986 (Folder 47: 12)
  Disposition form requesting clearance, letter, and note
- Army stealth task force, 1988 (Folder 47: 13)
  Letter, list of members for the Defense Science Board (DSB) sub-panel, program, and tentative agenda for the DSB task force on low observable technology
- American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) annual meeting, San Francisco, 1989 January 17 (Folder 47: 14)
  Invitation to join the panel on "SDI Testing and the ABM Treaty" and program
- Central Intelligence Agency (CIA), undated (Folder 47: 15)
  Miscellany